const STORE = [
    {
        question:'Who was the first hero to take on the name Green Lantern?',
        answers: [
            'Hal Jordon',
            'Alan Scott',
            'Guy Gardener',
            'Jhon Stewart',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Alan Scott',
        icon:'',
        alt:'Alan Scott first issue'
    },
    {
        question: 'What space sector is Earth in?',
        answers: [
            '2918',
            '1890',
            '2814',
            '2800',
        ],
        correctAnswer: '2814',
        icon:'',
        alt:''
    },
    {
        question: 'What power from the emotional spectrum does the Green Lantern Corps use?',
        answers:[
            'Compassion',
            'Love',
            'Hope',
            'Willpower',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Willpower',
    },
    {
        question: `Finish the Oath "In brightest day, in blackest night,
            no evil shall escape my sight. Let those who worship evil's might 
            ?????????????--GREEN LANTERN'S LIGHT!`,
        answers:[
            'beware my power',
            'fear and hide',
            'run and fear',
            'fear my might',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'beware my power',
    },
    {
        question: 'The guardians live on what planet?',
        answers:[
            'Oa',
            'Vogsphere',
            'Gallifrey',
            'Krypton',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Oa',
    },
    {
        question: 'Kyle Rayner was once a ??? before he was Green Lantern.',
        answers:[
            'teacher',
            'test piolt',
            'musician',
            'artist',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'artist',
    },
    {
        question: 'For a short time which member of the Green Lantern Coprs was the Mosaic?',
        answers:[
            'Hal Jordon',
            'Kilowog',
            `Ch'p`,
            'Jhon Stewart',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Jhon Stewart',
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the name of the entity of willpower?',
        answers:[
            'Ion',
            'Parallax',
            'Adara<br',
            'Proselyte',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Ion',
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of these Green Lanterns is also a living planet?',
        answers:[
            'Katma Tui',
            'Mogo',
            `Ke'Haan`,
            'Abin Sur',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Mogo',
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of these Corps boost the power of the Green Lantern with them?',
        answers:[
            'Indigo tribe',
            'Star Sapphire',
            'Blue Lantern',
            'Red Lantern',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Blue Lantern'
    }
];